agevs.com 2016-06-18

# 

## Privacy Policy

### Intro

Welcome to the abcmarine.info web site and online services (the "abcmarine.info"). abcmarine.info values the privacy of our members and others who visit and use the abcmarine.info (individually, "You" or collectively, "Users"). We take your privacy seriously and make it a priority to protect personally identifiable information that we obtain from and about individuals both online and off-line. 

abcmarine.info is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

By using the abcmarine.info (whether or not you are a registered member), you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this policy. If you do not want information about you to be used in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy, please do not use the abcmarine.info. 

abcmarine.info may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 03/16/2011.

### The Information abcmarine.info Collects

####  "Cookies" Information

When you visit the abcmarine.info, whether or not you are a registered member, we may send one or more cookies " small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters " to your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on a website. abcmarine.info may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the abcmarine.info. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. However, without cookies you will not have access to certain services on the abcmarine.info. Third party advertisements displayed in connection with the abcmarine.info may also contain cookies set by internet advertisers. We do not control these cookies and users of the abcmarine.info should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. 

### The Way abcmarine.info Uses Information

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### Anonymous Aggregated Data

Anonymous data is information (originally personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable) that subsequently is used in aggregate form. We may collect anonymous data whether or not you are a registered member of abcmarine.info. We may use anonymous data for purposes of research or analysis. We may conduct research on our customer demographics, internet usage, and interests and behavior based on personal data we gather. Although anonymous data may be based in part on personal data, it does not identify you personally. 

abcmarine.info may share this type of anonymous data with a variety of third parties, including its affiliates, advertisers, and other current and prospective business partners. abcmarine.info may use anonymous data collected for website administration, advertising, and promotional purposes, and we may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes. We may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows us to customize the advertising and marketing messages You receive while using the abcmarine.info. 

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### When abcmarine.info Discloses Information

abcmarine.info discloses automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist such parties in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the abcmarine.info. 

abcmarine.info may also disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. In some cases, we may make such disclosures without first providing notice to Users. 

abcmarine.info also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect abcmarine.info from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the abcmarine.info; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of abcmarine.info, our Users, or others. 

In the event that abcmarine.info is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

### Third-Party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

The abcmarine.info may be linked to internet websites operated by other companies. Some of these websites may be co-branded with our name or logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by us. abcmarine.info may also permit other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the abcmarine.info. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, some of the advertisements and links that appear on the abcmarine.info. These advertisers may automatically receive your IP address if this happens. These advertisers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party websites and third party ad servers or ad networks. abcmarine.info privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other third party advertisers or web sites. Please be aware that abcmarine.info does not warn you when you have chosen to link through to another website from the abcmarine.info. 

### abcmarine.info Contact Information

Please contact abcmarine.info with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices via support@abcmarine.info.
